The real, authentic and forceful power of the most high God
exercises through the faculties of Wise Man Christopher
as he prays for all present in The SCOAN auditorium for the salvation of their souls.
Here is a stiff opposition - a demon that had been hiding in this body,
exposed by the light of God.
Let us watch how darkness has no hiding place in this encounter with Wise Man Christopher.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
I am a simple spirit, just take it easy.
I am a gentleman, just take it easy.
Who are you in this body?
We are three.
Mention yourselves.
I am the queen of the coast, idol from his mother's house and idol from his father's house.
I can never leave this body because I love this man more than any other man.
But this is a man?
This person standing here is a man but I am a woman in him.
What are you doing in him?
He is my husband
As a wife, what have you done to this man, his career and his marriage?
This man you see here is a stupid man.
I told him not to have any affair with any woman,
that anything he wants in his life, I will give it to him.
He did not go to school; he only passed elementary 6
but he teaches in a secondary school.
I gave him brains.
If you see this man preaching, you will think that he is the one that wrote the Bible.
Since he cheated my love, he married a stupid woman.
Who is this stupid woman?
That woman - I am dragging him with that woman.
I told that woman that I would leave him for her but she must suffer.
There is somebody standing next to you, by your right.
Who is this woman to you?
I dont know her.
OK, let's find out from her. Madam, you are welcome.
Thank you, sir.
Who is this man to you?
He is my best.
It's a lie. I'm a pastor.
My husband - he is my best.
Tell her to go and look for her best. I'm not her best.
Madam, did you hear that?
Reverend Uche Ekeoma is my husband. We got married in 1990.
I wedded in 1978.
What is happening to her? What have you done so far to this marriage?
Sickness - she will suffer sickness very well in her life.
My name is Bianca, queen of the coast.
Every day, I stay with him, I always hear at night, "Bianca!"
He would be laughing and swimming on the bed.
Then I would wake up, put the light on, sit down
and ask him, "What is this? Who is this Bianca?" He would get annoyed with me.
The next thing he would do, if it was very early in the morning,
he would not take his bath; he would put on his clothes and go away.
For one year, I would not see him; I would look for him until I got him.
I have suffered.
Watch me and watch her. Who is more beautiful?
This is a man. Can a man be beautiful?
I am a woman, not a man.
Just look at me and this thing here. Then tell me who is more beautiful.
We wanted to come. I had been planning for this deliverance.
That morning, my elder sister gave me some money.
Other people and church members gave me up to 50,000 naira.
I then found myself in the hospital. My blood pressure was 300 --
I caused it.
I even took that money away. I just had mercy and she managed to go to hospital.
In that hospital, I should have killed her there.
You said that this man is a pastor; he preaches and calls the name Jesus.
How do you normally hide?
Sometimes, when I came to make love to him,
he would tell me, I am reading the Bible and praying.
This man could pray before but gradually, I swept everything out from him.
He cannot even pray well.
He cannot pray. Every night, I would quarrel with him.
Every morning, I would quarrel with him.
When I bring out my Bible to read, he would read and teach me what is in the Bible.
He would say, "Let me go and urinate".
Can a woman teach a woman the Bible?
Is it not a man that would teach a woman the Bible?
Ask her! Is it not a man, a pastor that would teach the members,
not a member to teach the pastor? Then why is she coming to me?
I am dragging one thing with her since she feels that I can teach her the Bible.
I cannot teach her the Bible because this man himself, he would throw the Bible away.
Right now, you demon, you can no longer hide.
I told you that I am a gentle spirit.
Don't release this fire because all your hand is fire, fire, fire!
As you are standing here - fire, fire, fire - and it is burning so high!
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Come out of him! Out!
Out!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
In Jesus' name. Amen.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
Rise up! You are delivered.
How are you, sir?
I'm fine, sir.
Ah! Why am I here?
Come, sir.
But I wore a coat.
You wore what?
I wore a coat.
Who removed it?
She removed it.
Who is she?
She is my best.
Good.
Are you a man or a woman?
I am a man. A full fledged man.
Good.
Look around.
Whose cloth is this?
It is my coat.
Who removed it?
I don't know.
Put it on. It is yours.
Thank You, Jesus!
How are you now, sir?
Sir, I am very free; I am happy now.
You said that you are the queen of the coast.
And you titled your name, 'Bianca'.
I am Reverend Ekeoma Uche. I am not a woman.
And many other things you said you have done.
You have destroyed yourself, your ministry and your marriage.
That demon that spoke through you is out!
Thank You, Jesus!
So Madam, you should not use it against him,
just as you should not use what she has said against her.
Both of you are completely delivered by Jesus!
TESTIMONY TIME
My name is Pastor Ekoma Uche from Abia State, Nigeria.
The woman standing beside me is my best - Prophetess Omoze Uche.
I was born into a Christian family but my grandfather was a native doctor.
When I was born, my mother told me that I was very sick; we were twins.
Because of my sickness, they decided to take me here and there to find a way to rescue my life.
At the last place that they went to, the native doctor told them to throw me inside the river
and expect to receive me back, which they did.
After three days, as my mother told me, they came to the river bank,
picked me up and I became well.
As I was growing up, something began to manifest in my life,
telling me that I could not make it until I recognised I came from somewhere".
Then, the next thing I did was to become a born-again Christian but the spirit was still in me.
So, I decided to enter Bible School even though the spirit was still operating in me.
Then, one day, I came to Lagos because it was the time of my graduation.
As I was returning to Aba, in the park, I saw a lady.
She just rushed to me with her car and said she wanted to join me in this journey.
I said that there was no problem since there was a vacant seat available.
We started the journey. On the road, she bought so many things.
It was on the trip, as we were seated that she then told me
she wanted to introduce herself to me and I agreed.
She introduced herself as Bianca and said she wanted to be my wife.
I said, "Okay".
While on the journey, she bought me a necklace, wristwatch and a ring.
When we got to Aba and I was about to go to my house,
she insisted that she would like to pass the night with me and we slept together.
As we were sleeping, something tapped me and I woke up.
I looked at her, and she began to change colour.
I wanted to scream but she woke up and asked me what was happening.
I became afraid.
Then she said, as long as I had slept with her, she had initiated me
and we entered into a covenant.
You mean she changed to what? Was it at midnight?
It was at midnight.
Were the lights off?
The lights were switched off but something tapped me and I awoke.
I turned on the light and saw her---
Change to what? Tell us.
Her legs were in the form of a fish while her upper body was that of a human being.
I wanted to scream, and she changed automatically
because she knew somebody would come in.
Okay, question again. The house was your own house or a rented house?
We slept in a hotel.
So you paid for the hotel?
She paid the money.
She paid the money?
Yes, because I did not have the money to pay for the hotel.
Okay, who located that hotel?
She located the hotel, although she asked me if I knew any hotel there.
I said, "No".
Then, you were a pastor?
Yes, I was a student pastor then.
Okay, in theology school?
Yes, sir.
Okay.
After then, my life changed.
One thing she told me to be in the covenant was that I would never have another wife.
I said, "Okay".
She told me that anytime I married, I would surely face the repercussions.
This lady gave me a talent such that I didn't even know what I was doing.
I did not go to secondary school; I just passed Primary Six.
However, I teach in secondary school as if I have graduated from university.
The subjects I was teaching in secondary school were government, geography, CRK
and the Igbo language.
She used to teach me at night.
The lady?
Yes.
Without attending any school?
Without attending any school - she physically came to me
during my time of study and taught me those subjects.
God is looking for character, not gifts.
What do you understand about that?
Gifted people are more among the children of satan than the children of God.
Gifted are more among the children of satan than even the children of God.
He is looking for character, not gifts.
God's Word reflects His character.
You can be gifted without character.
But you cannot have a good character without a gift.
There is what we call supernatural gift and natural gift - talent.
Let's listen to him.
Although I was a pastor, I was also a teacher.
She used to come and teach me; then I would teach the students.
Nobody in Aba does not know me as a teacher and also a pastor.
I teach students very well.
They loved me but they did not know that something was behind the lessons.
During the examination periods; that is, WAEC time,
I registered them, took them to the examination centres and we wrote.
On the day of writing the exams, if you did not agree with me, you would suffer in the hall.
After which I would grade them, I would make love with them,
play with them and initiate them.
When the results would come out, those who did not accept my offer,
or those who did not agree to give me what I required or needed from them,
their results would surely be seized.
Some people accused the government for seizing the exams.
Are you the one that seized their results?
Spiritually.
Their results would be seized spiritually.
If you settled us, we would ask you to go to the internet,
make your mark and then you could get your results.
When you got your results, you would find it very difficult to get admission to university.
Even if you got admission, it would be a fake result because it was from the spiritual world.
Remember that I told you that I was a 'Christian' and a pastor at the same time.
I was using all these things as a cover up.
It is not all results that the government seizes; some are seized by demons,
which is the simplest way to initiate them when they come back to us.
Can I ask you a question? If a student is a Christian,
coming as a student to your school or sitting the WAEC exams -
because they are not all your students, some students come from outside -
and they are Christians, what would you do with that?
If you are a Christian and I took you to the examination centre,
you are not my problem because if I dare come near you,
the fire around you will surely scare us away.
The question now: How many students are Christians today?
Every 10 students, two; and every 20 students, four.
Can your children be among these just two?
Every 10 students, two are fire.
The rest can be captured.
I know if I give you a chance today, some of our 'mummy' and 'daddy',
they will come and swear Heaven and earth that their children are eating with Jesus.
What you don't know, your children know better than you.
You don't need to send them to school; the internet has taught them everything.
They will just sit at home and be looking at you.
Sometimes, when you are battling with the television at home,
to switch it on with the remote, they will be looking at you.
After you have suffered so much, they will say, "Mummy, don't worry".
At the beginning, they would not want you to know that they know these things.
They will allow you to battle with the television or laptop.
After you have battled, they will say, "Mummy, don't worry. I know what is happening to it".
Because they don't want you to suspect that they are more advanced than you.
You will be using a handset, you will have loaded it with credit - full.
Your own children will not one day buy credit.
They will be deducting your credit; they will be using it.
You keep buying credit, and they are the ones using it.
Are you with me?
You will continue to load your handset with credit everyday
because you do not know anything - you are a zombie.
You don't know anything because you are too busy with your job.
There is a level you can go.
You continue to load your handset with credit.
You buy a card, and there is nothing left.
But your children at home, they will not one day buy credit.
They will be deducting.
When they know that you are shouting, they will stop it for a short time.
When you say, "Ah, what is happening to MTN? Why are they cutting my credit?
They keep on eating my credit!"
You don't know that your children at home are the ones eating your credit.
At that time, I had a secret room; I had not yet married then.
When pastors had their meetings, I would not go out that day.
Nothing would move me to go out of my room
because it would be the day we would meet in the spiritual world.
I would lock myself up in the room turn into a cat.
I would lock the room from the inside so that nobody could open it.
If I forgot to lock the room and you came inside, whatever you saw,
whatever happened to you would be your fault.
I would go to the spiritual world to have meetings.
If somebody opened that door and saw me, they would surely be initiated.
I was also a pastor then
Before I met my wife, this spiritual wife gave me two powers:
whatever I spoke would happen and in my eyes, I had a seduction spirit.
Whether you are married or not, if I liked you, I would get you,
no matter where you run to.
That is, those who are not Christians because we do not have anything to do with Christians.
When I saw my wife, I thought she was the kind of person I wanted to marry.
I looked at her and as our eyes met, I seduced her because at that time,
she was about to marry somebody else.
Since that person had not officially married her, I claimed her to be my wife.
Though she hated me at that time, she began to have an interest in me
and whatever I asked her to do, she did.
There was a day I went to my elder brother who had money.
I asked him to give me sixty naira to get a passport
because there was a job I wanted to secure.
He brought out a bunch of money and showed it to me and said,
"You are my brother, go and look for your own money".
I said, "No problem" and left him.
Since that time till now, my elder brother is now doing a petty business in a local market.
He is nothing to write home about.
Last week, I was delivered.
So, since the beginning of your life, that evil spirit has been tormenting you?
It tormented me but I clothed myself with 'Christianity'
and with the name 'pastor' but nobody knew.
If I came to your church or if I was preaching,
you must surely come out when I call an altar call because they saw me as a pastor.
So you preach very well?
I preach very well, sir.
My wife is a prophetess.
She is a prophetess indeed but the other way round.
We started having disagreements and quarrels.
My spiritual wife did not allow her to have peace of mind.
Okay.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Speak out! Who are you?
We are three.
Mention yourselves.
Idol from the mother's house, spiritual husband, and she is a queen.
How do you operate in this body?
We gave her anger and barrenness.
Any time she was pregnant, we would come as a nurse.
She would deliver into our hands and we would leave with the child.
She used to go to spiritual doctors and thought she was going for protection.
Look at it here.
What is that?
We entered through this place.
Touch the place.
Look at it.
Look at the flowers here; we entered through there.
I wanted to kill her in the late 80's.
The first man who wanted to marry her - we gave her a drug addict and seller.
She refused.
They took her to a place where they told her that if she married a pastor,
she would suffer and not give birth to a child.
She became pregnant and we took another one, that was in 2001, when she had a son.
The other three boys, four in all, we took them all.
She is crying every minute of the day.
What have you done to her career?
She is a prophetess. I have finished everything about her career.
I closed the church down.
What have you done to her husband?
Does she have a husband?
OK, let's find out because we are seeing a man standing next to her.
You are welcome, sir.
Who is this woman to you?
She is my married wife; I married her as tradition demands.
OK, let's find out. Who is this man to you?
This man here is a snatcher. He snatched my wife from me.
Are you a snatcher, sir?
I am not a snatcher.
What have you done to this man?
I pushed him to women.
He would be going from one woman to another.
This idiot would cry.
She would call him on the phone but he would not answer her.
When she cries, we are happy. We would be teasing her.
Sir, did you listen to what she said?
I heard her.
What can you say about what she said?
The life she lives as a pastor, I am always ashamed to walk with her on the road.
She smokes.
In fact, I am enduring because I love her.
She said she is a pastoress, a prophetess. Are you confirming this to be true?
Yes.
What about you? Who are you, sir?
I am also a pastor, a minister.
I gave her cigarettes in the dream and she smoked when she was young -
about 13 years old.
The day I found out that she liked cigarettes, I was shocked.
She said she could not do without cigarettes.
She started smoking when she was in Primary Six.
What else have you done to this woman?
Sickness - I gave her hypertension, diabetes and waist pain.
I gave her serious headaches and general body pain - from head to toe.
What can you say about it?
It is true. She can never sleep without drugs.
Right now, you contrary spirit, this body belongs to Jesus. Get out!
Come out of this body!
Out!
All over your body, Holy Ghost fire!
Come out of her!
Every part of your body!
Thank You, Lord, for her deliverance.
In Jesus' name!
Amen.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Hallelujah.
Rise up. You are delivered.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
How are you, Madam?
I am fine.
You said that you possessed a contrary spirit that destroyed your marriage life,
gave you the spirit of smoking and also destroyed your career.
I have been crying.
People said that I was a good woman.
But I didn't see anything good in me because I used to smoke.
Thank You, Jesus!
Right now, how do you feel within you after the deliverance?
I am okay.
Who is this man to you?
He is my best.
Is he not a snatcher?
Thank You, Jesus!
Her past is over. She is delivered.
Don't use it against her. Otherwise you too will be tempted.
Thank You, Jesus!
My name is Prophetess Mrs Omoze Uche.
Ah, Prophetess?
Yes, sir.
We come from Aba (Nigeria).
It all started when I was living with my grandmother
and she told me anything I ate in the dream, I should try and eat it physically.
When I was younger, I smoked in my dreams.
When I woke up, I went to a store where they sold cigarettes.
The people in the shop asked me who had sent me to buy the cigarettes.
I told them that it was my elder brother.
They asked me the name of the cigarettes.
I told them that I didn't know but pointed at them
because they were the ones I smoked in my dreams.
You have been smoking for how many years now?
It has been about 25 years. I smoked a packet of cigarettes every day.
After your deliverance?
Since Sunday, I have no urge to smoke.
I don't even remember smoking.
Rise up! She said she doesn't even remember, talkless of smoking.
Do you know that this is the problem of the whole world?
If I am talking, let me see your hand.
50% of people in the world are addicted to smoking.
And after smoking, they can do anything, they can commit suicide.
She said that after the deliverance, she does not even remember, talkless thinking of the urge.
She does not even remember that she was smoking before.
Just like that.
Viewers all over the world, did you listen to that?
If you are a smoker, just come for deliverance.
Jesus will deliver you.
Thank you. You may be seated.
So enough is enough. Satan has no room again in your life.
I did a lot of things in this life, in the name of Christianity.
My advice to people, particularly pastors and parents:
Look and know who is who in your church
because there are pastors who claim to be pastors but they are not.
Please, whatever you are doing in this life,
make sure you are not a goat in sheep's clothing.
Thank you. Let's hear from the woman.
I thank God today for the man of God and the wise men
who He used to deliver me and my husband.
There is an instruction now from God.
My brother there, I want you, with respect, remove your collar.
Let's later ask God whether you are called to the work of God.
You remove your collar.
I would like you to personally address yourselves as Mr and your wife as Mrs now to the whole world.
Later, after the service, we will come together and ask God what His direction is.
You have given pain to your own kingdom, not the Kingdom of God.
We are free moral agents. You can choose not to submit to satan.
And you can choose not to submit today.
You submitted to satan, and satan used you mightly
because we remember when you said a woman entered the vehicle
and you people entered and she carried you to a hotel; it was somebody you didn't know.
If she had used you for a ritual at the hotel, definitely, nobody would have known.
I will not leave you unless God gives us the direction you should follow,
to really show that you regret the way satan used you.
Now, I am telling the whole world that our names are Mr and Mrs Ekeoma Uche,
not Pastor and Prophetess Uche Ekeoma.
I will pray with you to ask God the direction for your life -
whether God wants you to be an engineer or go back to do the work of teaching
or lawyer or whatever. We can now ask God.
Or if it is the work of God, God wants you to do, you will now begin to...
Not that name you bore before now. Okay?
I apologise to the world for the name I was moving with as a pastor.
Now I believe that God will grant me the grace, in Jesus' name.
Can we hear from your wife?
My name now is Mrs Omoze Uche Ekeoma, not Prophetess Okeoma Uche.
I apologise to the world.
Let the will of God, through the man of God, be done in our lives.
Thank you. Rise up and give thanks to God.
Just bow down your head
and let's come together and pray to God to show His mercy upon humankind.
Bow down your head and ask God for His mercy and favour
and that He should continue to show His mercy.
His mercy and favour will never end.
Thank You, Lord. In Jesus Christ's name.
You may be seated. Thank you.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations and Changing the world.